{
    "id": "21ceb77ea4fa43568809b751bc294c0a",
    "title": "All vs. Every",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I  visit him .................................. other day.",
            "description": "Use every with singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46acbd63cf2f40cf93ce2f273d6936ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Buses leave ..................................... 15 minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "584edca8a7f549a0b428c82bb60ab026"
        },
        {
            "question": "I answered ........................................ the questions.",
            "description": "All is used with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ad3a6f11ec148ffba4956240465e167"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was working ................................ day yesterday.",
            "description": "All day means from morning to evening.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00fc4786b3914c83a4cf3e82834abad9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She drank ................................... the water in the bottle.",
            "description": "Either all or all of is possible here.  All is used with plural and uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "all of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa34457d45db4bcaa8e27055f2bddbdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has invited ................................... of you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4015037ba97e4b67954c142940493acc"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. my family live in different parts of India.",
            "description": "Before a noun with a determiner, all and all of are both possible.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Everyone",
                "All of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c32649a235574140a1503792ac955b68"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was crying ..................................... the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e24511dcc37451090aae37ad1e45e52"
        },
        {
            "question": "She lost .......................................... in the war.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "everything"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "540bed64872949b99003d8ccb89d1636"
        },
        {
            "question": "She lost ..................................... that she owned in the disaster.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eeab6d5e62854ed0b18b658510af50ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ I want is something to eat and drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Everything"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5cb34620a10b4d63b445b937e95b8e08"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. stood up.",
            "description": "All does not normally mean everybody.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Everybody"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6f81d51690846d78a2c486cfcfb133b"
        }
    ]
}